I was lost before I knew what living felt like Breathing didn't mean I was alive
I was falling, I was stalling Every second felt like crawling
I was smiling just to hide it But the silence kept on calling
I was drowning in my head Every thought was getting violent
I was wishing I'd go numb Just to make the noise go quiet
I was tired of the mornings Tried to wake in just to ache
I was praying for an end And I was scared enough to take
I was living in a mirror Where I couldn't see my face
Just a body full of damage Trying to occupy some space
And I didn't want to die I just didn't want to stay
In a life where every breath Felt borrowed anyway
I was standin’ on the edge, not to jump but to escape
From a mind that kept on tellin’ me I’d never be okay
But you, you saw the light in me When I was seeing none
You held my hand when every part of me would run
You turned the nights I wanted Gone into the nights I survived
You didn't save my life But you showed me why
And you, you took my worst point And made it something real
You made me want to wake up Just to see how joy can feel
Now I'm standing where the sky Don't feel so far above
I was down there with the shadows Now I'm up here learning love
I was buried in the past Every memory away
Every it'll get better Felt a little bit too late
I would stare into the dark Like it understood my pain
Like the void was the only thing That never looked away
Then you walked in like a sunrise I didn't plan to see
Didn't ask me to be perfect Just to stay and try with me
You ain't fix me with a sentence You ain't rush me through the hurt
You just sat with all my broken Showed me I still had some worth
You never said I was weak For the thoughts in my head
You just told me stay here When I wanted to end
And I hate how close I came To never knowing your name
But I'm here and that's proof That I don't think the same
Cause you, you saw the light in me When I was seeing none
You held my hand When every part of me would run
You turned the nights I wanted Gone into the nights I survived
You didn't save my life But you showed me why
And you, you made a future Feel like something I could choose
Turned my fear into a reason not to lose
Now I wake up feeling proud of Just staying alive
I was down there with the demons Now I'm up here, I'm alright
Some days the thoughts still whisper low Like echoes from a life I used to know
But now they don't control the room They just knock
I don't let them through Cause I've seen
What it's like to feel okay I felt peace, sit still
And actually stay And when my mind starts slipping back
I remember how you pulled me back
I was breaking, now I'm building I was scared of all my feelings
I was stuck inside the question Now I'm living in the meaning
I don't say I'm here forever But I'm better than before
I don't beg the night to end I don't hate the morning anymore
And if I ever start forgetting What it took to get me here
I'll remember how you stood beside me When my future disappeared
Cause you, you saw the light in me When I was seeing none
You held my hand When every part of me would run
You turned the nights I wanted gone Into the nights I survived
You didn't save my life But you showed me why
And now Now I'm breathing like the world don't want me gone
Now I'm dreaming like my heart can still move on
I was falling, I was lost I was ready to say goodbye
Now I'm here, and I'm happy I stayed alive
I was down there Thinking I'd never get free
Now I’m up here… And life finally feels like me